Sai Dilip Reddy O Featured

Data Science Al Engineer seeking roles in Software Development, Application Programming, Technology Management, Requirement Gathering, Data Extraction, Data Validation, Statistical Modeling, Data Analysis, Machine Learning, Python, MySQL, Linux, JavaScript, Unix



Current Designation: Data Science Al Engineer Total Experience: 5 Year(s) 6 Month(s)

Current Company: FAB bank Notice Period: 1 Month

Current Location: Dubai Highest Degree: M.Tech [Computers]

Pref. Location: Dubai, Kuwait, United Arab Emirates (UAE)
Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: Banking/Financial Services/Broking

Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Key Skills: Data Science AI Engineer, Software Developer, keras, tensorflow, Development, Application

Programming, Technology Management, Requirement Gathering, Data Extraction, Data Validation, Statistical Modeling, Data

Analysis, Machine Learning, Python, MySQL, Linux, JavaSc

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 21-Jan-21 Last Modified: 21-Jan-21

Summary

5+ years Experienced Subject Matter Expert with a demonstrated history of working in the information technology and product industry. Expert in Machine learning, preparing models based on algorithms - Supervised and Unsupervised Learning, NLP and Deep Learning. Skilled in Requirements Analysis, Data Extraction, Preparation, Visualization, Statistical Data Analysis and Statistical Modeling. Experienced in working with python, sklearn, tensor-flow, MXNet, Al, DL package Have knowledge on using ML & DL skills in DSP. Worked on different types of data formats like JSON,XMI.TXT, Images.

Work Experience

FAB bank as Data Science Al Engineer

Mar 2020 to Till Date

Classification of business mails box and preparing category folders and pushing mails into category folders based on the classification result, Computer vision service using Azure Machine learning, Al, Data science techniques

Etisalat as Software Engineer

Mar 2019 to Feb 2020

Developing Fully AI-based web portal for on-hand stock resources Inventory Demand forecasting tracking and Error tracking on CISCO DEVICES, and management using Machine learning, AI,Data science techniques.

Aadhya-Analytics as Software Engineer

Jun 2015 to Feb 2019

Developed Expertise solutions in all the key requirements of Machine learning problems like text analytics, image processing, object detection, Al bot preparation for the in-house projects and Retail clients.

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Electronics and Computer Engineering) from USHA RAMA COLLEGE OF ENGINEERING AND **TECHNOLOGY** in 2015

PG: M.Tech (Computers) from Jawaharlal Nehru Technological University (JNTU) KAKINADA in 2018

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version	Last Used Experience	
Python, Tensor flow, CNN		2020	5 Year(s) 0 Month(s)
pandas, scikit module		2020	5 Year(s) 0 Month(s)
SAS ESP,SAS,SAS		2020	3 Year(s) 0 Month(s)
contextual analyser,MongoDB.		2020	5 Year(s) 1 Month(s)
MySQL,Linux,JavaScript,Unix		2020	5 Year(s) 0 Month(s)

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English				
Hindi				
Telugu				

Affirmative Action

Work Authorization

Category: General

Job Type: Permanent

Physically Challenged: No

Employment Status: Full time